Facilities Planning Building File 1945-1980
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Humanities Building - Bldg. 803
  - Fred Bassetti & Co., Arch., Corres., 1968-1972 (Box 6, Folder 335)
  - George C. Izenour & Assoc., Corres., 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 336)
  - Fred Bassetti & Co., Arch., Contract & C.O.s (Box 6, Folder 337)
- Child & Family Studies Center - Bldg. 804
  - Budget (Box 6, Folder 338)
  - Warren, Cummings, Heylman, Archs., Schematic Design (Box 6, Folder 339)
  - Building Program (Box 6, Folder 340)
  - General Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 341)
  - Warren, Cummings, Heylman, Archs., Corres., 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 342)
  - Warren, Cummings, Heylman, Archs., Contract & C.O.s (Box 6, Folder 343)
- Poultry Building-Puyallup - Bldg. 1000
  - General Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 344)
  - General Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 345)
  - Brudevold & Putnam, Archs., Corres., 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 346)
  - Brudevold & Putnam, Archs., Contract & C.O.s (Box 6, Folder 347)
  - Prime Construction Co., Corres., 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 348)
  - Prime Construction Co., Contract, Payments, C.O.s (Box 6, Folder 349)
  - Office & Lab Penthouse Louvers, Prime Cons., Contract, Payments, C.O.s (Box 6, Folder 350)
  - Rejected Bids (Box 6, Folder 351)
- Sewer Extention - Puyallup
  - General Correspondence, 1967-1973 (Box 6, Folder 352)
  - L.R. Steele Construction, Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 353)
  - L.R. Steele Construction, Contract & C.O.s (Box 6, Folder 354)
  - Rejected Bids (Box 6, Folder 355)
- SW Washington Experiment Station, Vancouver
  - General Correspondence, 1948-1958 (Box 6, Folder 356)
- Two Pre-Fab Storage Sheds, SWWES, Vancouver
  - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 357)
  - Rose City Pre-Cut Buildings, Inc., Corres., 1963 (Box 6, Folder 358)
  - Rose City Pre-Cut Buildings, Inc., Contract & C.O.s (Box 6, Folder 359)
  - Rejected Bids (Box 6, Folder 360)